for any YouTube video you can download a
written transcript or the subtitles of
the video this is especially useful for
example if you want to study what
someone is saying or you want to edit
your own video into a blog post so let
me show you an example using one of my
own videos and here it is I just
uploaded this video a few hours ago and
the transcript is already available
it only takes YouTube a few hours to
have their artificial intelligence sense
into what the person is saying and
create a transcript so when you go to
any youtube video scroll down and
underneath the video by the way I'm
assuming you are using a laptop or a
desktop computer do this scroll down and
then click the three dots underneath the
video three dots there and then click on
open transcript alright so here's what
you do you're gonna have to it's if you
want to for example edit this into a
blog post you want to toggle so that the
timestamps are no longer there and you
do this by clicking the three dots here
once you've opened the transcript click
on the three dots here inside the
transcript and click on toggle
timestamps alright now that the
timestamps are gone what I'd like to do
is I'd like to scroll down to the very
bottom so quickly scroll down to the
very bottom and then once I'm at the
very bottom whoops
the very bottom here I click and select
going upwards I find that this is easier
and has fewer sort of Mouse errors if I
do it from the bottom up instead of from
the top down you can experiment yourself
but anyway try that and once you have
selected it what you need to do then is
to do command C on your keyboard if
you're on a Mac or on Windows its ctrl C
to copy it to your invisible clipboard
and then open up a new tab and what I
like to do is use Google Docs so I'm
gonna type in doc dot new and in case
you don't know that automatically opens
up a new Google document
your private Google Drive so now that I
have paste copied the transcript I'm
going to click on edit paste without
formatting so that it just plain text
and there it is there's the entire video
transcript based on you know YouTube's
artificial intelligence it's not going
to be perfect but it's certainly a great
start to editing this into a blog post
all right I hope that's helpful and I'll
see you in the next video